<Document>
    <title>Lucy Robillard - About</title>
    <description>A little bit about me, my contact information, and my public GPG key.</description>
    <body>
        &lt;div style="text-align: center;">
            &lt;h1>About&lt;/h1>
            &lt;img src="./media/larobitrumpet.png" alt="Lucy Robillard's icon, a 64x64 pixel image that shows a trumpet with the colors of the non-binary pride flag playing two eighth notes on top of a computer with a keyboard colored with the colors of the seven striped lesbian sunset pride flag, displaying on it's screen a circle containing the genderfae pride flag with the sunset aroace pride flag in the background, all behind the transgender pride flag." style="border: solid #000 3px; width: 60vw; max-width: 512px; image-rendering: pixelated;">
        &lt;/div>
			&lt;p>Hello, I am Lucy Robillard. I am a silly little genderfae transbian trying to make her way in the world. I am currently serving as an AmeriCorps Member at City Year where I serve as a near-peer mentor and tutor in a 3rd grade classroom, providing extra support, hosting small groups, and planning and executing school-wide events and bulletin boards in an undeserved community in Sacramento, California. I got my undergrad in computer science from the University of California, Davis in 2025, and I earned an Associate in Science for Transfer in Mathematics and an Associate of Science in Natural Science from Sierra College in 2022. I enjoy programming and computer science and you will find some of my projects on this website. I am a musician and have been playing trumpet since 2011, and I am currently playing trumpet in the Video Game Orchestra at UC Davis.&lt;/p>
        &lt;div style="text-align: center;">
            &lt;h1>Contact&lt;/h1>
            &lt;p style="text-align: center;">You can contact me via email: &lt;a href="mailto:larobitrumpet@lucyrobillard.xyz">larobitrumpet@lucyrobillard.xyz&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
            &lt;p style="text-align: center;">If you have a ProtonMail account and want to use that, you can email: &lt;a href="mailto:larobitrumpet@protonmail.com">larobitrumpet@protonmail.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
            &lt;p style="text-align: center;">My GitHub can be found here: &lt;a target="blank_" href="https://github.com/larobitrumpet">github.com/larobitrumpet&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
            &lt;p style="text-align: center;">My public GPG key can be found here: &lt;a target="blank_" href="pubkey.txt">GPG key&lt;/a>.
            &lt;p>You can run this command to automatically download my GPG key and add it to your keyring:&lt;/p>
            &lt;pre>&lt;code>curl -L https://lucyrobillard.xyz/pubkey.txt | gpg --import&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
        &lt;/div>
        &lt;div style="text-align: center;">
            &lt;h1>Social Media&lt;/h1>
            &lt;p style="text-align: center;">Mastodon: &lt;a rel="me" target="_blank" href="https://tech.lgbt/@larobitrumpet">@larobitrumpet@tech.lgbt&lt;/a>&lt;p>
        &lt;/div>
    </body>
</Document>
