<Document>
    <title>Lucy Robillard - Music</title>
    <description>Some of the musical performances I have done.</description>
    <body>
        &lt;h1>Music&lt;/h1>
        &lt;p>This is where you can find some of my performances.&lt;/p>
    </body>
    <entry>
        <level>2</level>
        <indent_num>2</indent_num>
        <title>Performances</title>
        <description>Here are some of my performances.</description>
        <summary>Click to see performances.</summary>
        <entry>
            <level>3</level>
            <indent_num>5</indent_num>
            <title>Video Game Orchestra</title>
            <description>Video Game Orchestra is a student run orchestra at UC Davis that plays music from video games. Video Game Orchestra holds a concert at the end of every quarter. You can check out their website here: &lt;a href="https://vgoatucd.weebly.com/" target="_blank">vgoatucd.weebly.com&lt;/a>.</description>
            <summary>Click to see Video Game Orchestra concerts.</summary>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>Fall 2022 - Hidden Gems: The Music of Indie Games</title>
                <description>Our theme for the fall 2022 quarter was indie game music. This concert explores music from popular indie games as well as some less popular hidden gems. Music includes The Waters Above from Sky: Children of Light, Core Keeper Medley from Core Keeper, In the Blood from Hades, Hopes and Dreams from Undertale, Nascence and Apotheosis from Journey, and a variety of pieces performed by small ensembles.</description>
                <youtube>videoseries?list=PLjhZllVrs_FpKXPSsj5FSY_NPNWTB-Ou6</youtube>
            </entry>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>Winter 2023 - In Another World</title>
                <description>Our theme for winter 2023 was music from distopian and apocalyptic games. Music includes: Main Theme from Fallout 4 and Fallout: New Vegas, Aloy's Theme from Horizon: Zero Dawn, Song of Ancients from Nier: Automata, Snake Eater from Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater, Main Theme from Chrono Trigger, Aerith's Theme from Final Fantasy VII, and Theme from Super Smash Bros. Brawl, as well as a variety of music performed by small ensembles.</description>
				<youtube>videoseries?list=PLjhZllVrs_FqiON8DnAuj3YY-nRb3Zrd-</youtube>
            </entry>
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <level>3</level>
            <indent_num>5</indent_num>
            <title>Granite Bay Emerald Brigade - Field Shows</title>
            <description>The Granite Bay Emerald Brigade is the marching band at Granite Bay High School. I have performed in four field shows with the Emerald Brigade.</description>
            <summary>Click to see field shows.</summary>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>2019 - Area 51</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Emerald Brigade performing our 2019 field show "Area 51" at WBA Grand Championship Prelims. I would like to point out that the idea and initial design for this show began before the storm area 51 meme. Music includes: Gavorkna Fanfare by Jack Stamp, the X Files theme, M.I.B. Main Theme by Danny Elfman, On the Waterfront Main Title by Leonard Bernstein, Uninvited by Alanis Morissette, Bodysnatchers by Radiohead, and Paranoid Android by Radiohead.</description>
                <youtube>rZAbRh91naU</youtube>
            </entry>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>2018 - Odyssey to a New World</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Emerald Brigade performing our 2018 field show "Odyssey to a New World" at Folsom high school. The show follows the journey of a traveler taking the Transcontinental Railroad west to the "New World". The our season was cut short due to forest fires causing the air quality be deemed unsafe for field shows, and thus we were never able to perform this field show in a WBA circuit. The show we performed at Folsom is unfinished, but it was the last show we were able to perform. Music includes music from New World Symphony by Antonín Dvořák.</description>
                <youtube>2TkgHlK7XLc</youtube>
            </entry>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>2017 - Flight 19: Lost in the Bermuda Triangle</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Emerald Brigade performing our 2017 award winning field show "Lost in the Bermuda Triangle" at WBA Grand Championship Finals where we won in division 4A. The show is inspired by the real life story of the training mission Flight 19 getting lost in the Bermuda Triangle on December 5, 1945 and was never found. Music includes: Undertow by John Mackey, Lightning Field by John Mackey, and music from Castaway.</description>
                <youtube>Vqox47kjyhY</youtube>
            </entry>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>2016 - Through the Dark Forest</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Emerald Brigade performing our 2016 field show "Through the Dark Forest" at James Logan High School. While we did perform at WBA Grand Championship Finals, due to weather conditions, the competition was canceled shortly after we performed. Music includes: Serenada Schizophrana by Danny Elfman, Enjoy The Silence by Eric Whitacre, and Ride.</description>
                <youtube>tYe6UxXtb4o</youtube>
            </entry>
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <level>3</level>
            <indent_num>5</indent_num>
            <title>Granite Bay Emerald Brigade - Winter Percussion</title>
            <description>Granite Bay High School also has a Winter Percussion group. I have performed in four of their shows, but I could only find videos for two of them.</description>
            <summary>Click to see winter percussion shows.</summary>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>2019-2020 - On the Verge of Chaos</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Winter Percussion performing our show "On the Verge of Chaos" at Bandtastic. This video includes two performances, one standing still, and one with movement. Unfortunately, our season was cut short due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The show is largely unfinished and the ending was never fully fleshed out.</description>
                <youtube>89GdHpk6hH0</youtube>
            </entry>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>2018-2019 - Breath</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Winter Percussion performing our show "Breath" at NCPA Championships in Stockton.</description>
                <youtube>oPp-uiLBI5s</youtube>
            </entry>
        </entry>
        <entry>
            <level>3</level>
            <indent_num>5</indent_num>
            <title>Grantie Bay High School Baritone Choir</title>
            <description>The Granite Bay High School Baritone Choir was created by Susana Peoples in order to grow the choir program by creating a group for lower voices. I have performed with the Baritone Choir a few times, but I have only found a video for one performance.</description>
            <summary>Click to see Baritone Choir performance.</summary>
            <entry>
                <level>4</level>
                <indent_num>8</indent_num>
                <title>May 22, 2019 - Spring Concert</title>
                <description>This is the Granite Bay Baritone Choir performing at the spring concert in 2019. Songs include the Mickey Mouse Barbershop Tag and Viva L'Company.</description>
                <youtube>jK3J-yCX6EM</youtube>
            </entry>
        </entry>
    </entry>
<!--    <entry>
        <level>2</level>
        <indent_num>2</indent_num>
        <title>Compositions</title>
        <description>Here are some of my compositions.</description>
        <summary>Click to see compositions.</summary>
    </entry> -->
</Document>
